Public Journal UP049
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Public Journal
2005 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP049
0.75 Linear Feet
6 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Public Journal and Web crawls.
Biographical / Historical
The Public Journal student organization began publication of a creative writing journal in Spring, 2005. Founder Daniela Perdomo sought to provide greater freedom of expression for contributors by removing the authors' names from published works. A list of contributors is presented at the being on the journal, but individual authors are not identified for the pieces. From 2007-2009, the organization experimented with creating a true "Public Journal" when they left a notebook in the Tisch Library Tower Cafe and allowed anyone to write in it anonymously.
The organization is overseen by the Media Advocacy Board.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Public Journal student literary journal and web crawls documenting its web presence. Some issues are available only in electronic format.
Student life
- Public Journal, 2005 -- 2018; UP049.001; 0.75 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of the Public Journal student literary journal.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Public Journal, 2005-04; UP049.001.001.00001
    Issue
    1
  - Public Journal, 2005-05; UP049.001.001.00002
    2
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2005; UP049.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    3
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2006; UP049.001.001.00004
    4
  - Public Journal, 2006-12; UP049.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    5
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2007; UP049.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    6
  - Public Journal, 2007-12; UP049.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    7
  - Public Journal, 2008-04; UP049.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    Childhood Trauma Issue.
    8
  - Public Journal, 2007 -- 2009; UP049.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    Library Issue. Notebook was left in the Tower Cafe of Tisch Library for students to add to between fall 2007 and spring 2009. No facsimile of the Journal was published.
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2009; UP049.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    9
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2010; UP049.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    10
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2010; UP049.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    11
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2011; UP049.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2012; UP049.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2012; UP049.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2013; UP049.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2013; UP049.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2014; UP049.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2014; UP049.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2015; UP049.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2015; UP049.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2016; UP049.001.002.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Public Journal, Spring, 2017; UP049.001.002.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2017; UP049.001.002.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Public Journal, Spring 2018; UP049.000030 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Public Journal, Fall, 2018; UP049.001.002.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UP049.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Public Journal website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Tufts Public Journal, 2015 -- 2020; UP049.002.00001
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.